let questions = [];

questions[0] = {
    question: 'Is this a question?',
    rightAnswer: 0,
    answers: [
        'yes',
        'no',
    ]
}

questions[1] = {
    question: 'What is a quiz',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'something lol',
        'idk',
    ]
}

questions[2] = {
    question: 'What is the meaning of life',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'to eat prawns',
        'idk',
        'to make js quizes',
    ]
}

questions[3] = {
    question: 'Is this a question?',
    rightAnswer: 0,
    answers: [
        'yes',
        'no',
    ]
}

questions[4] = {
    question: 'What is a quiz',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'something lol',
        'idk',
    ]
}

questions[5] = {
    question: 'What is the meaning of life',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'to eat prawns',
        'idk',
        'to make js quizes',
    ]
}

questions[6] = {
    question: 'What is the meaning of life',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'to eat prawns',
        'idk',
        'to make js quizes',
    ]
}

questions[7] = {
    question: 'Is this a question?',
    rightAnswer: 0,
    answers: [
        'yes',
        'no',
    ]
}

questions[8] = {
    question: 'What is a quiz',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'something lol',
        'idk',
    ]
}

questions[9] = {
    question: 'What is the meaning of life',
    rightAnswer: 1,
    answers: [
        'to eat prawns',
        'idk',
        'to make js quizes',
    ]
}